

CONTACT ME AT

• Flutstrasße 26, Kleve 47533

gzabala1603@yahoo.com

WEBSITE

https://avilaweb.github.io/CV.marketing.github.ie/

SKILLS SUMMARY

•••• ZOOM

••• Google docs, Google meeting

•••• Excel

•••• PowerPoint

•••• Grammarly

••• CSS

•••• HTML

••• Bootstrap

LANGUAGES

English C1

Spanish Native

Dutch B1

GABRIEL ZABALA

INTERNATIONAL BUSINESS & MANAGEMENT

PERSONAL PROFILE

Highly motivated, creative, and versatile professional/student with a growth mindset and high learning agility. Experience in the fields of Marketing, Webdevelopment, business, and content creation.

I am Cheerful & enthusiastic with positive energy and a cando attitude.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Polyglot Kids. Düsseldorf, Germany

English and Spanish tutor | Oct 2020 - present

- I am an English and Spanish private tutor that provides online and face-to-face lessons to students of all levels who want to improve their language skills.
- I give English and Spanish camps to groups of students that want to have fun while improving their language skills

WAYS4WATER

Digital Marketing - Web Development 2021-present

 Ways4Water is a startup that aims to clean the waters of the Rhein in Germany and nearby rivers. I help the company come up with a mission statement online and code the website of the company

Munerix

Web development and content design 2021 Freelance

• I co-worked with the owner of the company Munerix to give a fresh look to the business appereance online.

ZUYD Hogeschool Ambassador

Student Ambassador 2020

• I manage excel tasks to source events and provide promotional talks to attract prospective students.

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

International Business and Communication Diploma

Zuyd Hogeschool - University of applied Sciences: The Netherlands | 2020

Financial Markets YALE course

Course on finances giving by YALE online (scholarship)

International Business and Management

Rhein-Waal University 2021 - current year

International Management IU university - London Business School

University of applied sciences and London Business School 2022-current year

Digital Marketing

Open University - Google garage 2020

TEFL diploma to teach English

i-to-i official diploma CELTA equivalent

High school diploma

San Antonio del Tuy Venezuela 2019

ACADEMIC ACHIEVEMENTS

Excellence scholarship

Zuyd Hogeschool - University of applied Sciences: The Netherlands 2020

Financial Markets YALE HONORS

Course on finances giving by YALE graduated with honors and a (scholarship)